humber.ca 2017-11-19

# Privacy Policy | Humber College

## Privacy & Security Statement

Humber is committed to respecting your privacy and protecting your personal information whether you are browsing for information or conducting business with us electronically. This Privacy & Security Statement explains the current practices employed at our web sites and is based upon the principles covered in Canada's Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act ("PIPEDA") as well as Ontario's Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act ("FIPPA").

## Privacy of Personal Information.

Humber does not share personal information that is provided voluntarily through web forms or other means, including standard web server log files. If you have supplied your email address, Humber may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Humber and our products.

## Web Server Log Files

Humber uses standard web server log files to collect site visitation statistics. Web server logging does collect machine-specific information such as IP address, operating system, and web browser type. Logs may also provide information about user pathways through the web site. The College collects this information in order to understand how its web site is used and to plan for future enhancements to the web site.

## Cookies

The web site uses cookies. Cookies support the site visitation statistics process and support functions such as forms processing. Visitors to our web site may reject any or all of our cookies by using their web browser's preferences. Site visitors should be aware that certain features of the web site, such as forms and surveys, require the use of cookies to function properly.

## Trademarks

Humber and all other names, logos, seals, or other symbols that are representative of the College are trademarks of use. Reproduction, copying, or redistribution of trademarks, without the written permission of Humber, is prohibited.

## General Web Disclaimer

Humber makes web resources available to all of the community but does not review, edit, or endorse all items accessible from these pages.

Personal and non-departmental web pages are not official statements of the College, and Humber is not responsible for the content of these page. We strive to ensure the accuracy of material on the web but discrepancies may exist between printed and electronic information. In any such case please contact the site owner directly.

Opinions expressed in personal or non-departmental web pages should be construed as those of their authors, who are solely responsible for the information contained therein. If you have questions or comments about a particular page or document, please contact its site owner.

Some web pages contain links to web pages created by sources outside of the College. The existence of these links does not suggest any implicit or explicit approval of or endorsement of the linked web pages and their content by the College.

If you have any general comments, suggestions, questions, or concerns about Humber's web pages, please direct them to [webmaster@humber.ca](mailto:webmaster@humber.ca).

Although Humber does not routinely screen or monitor content posted by users to the web site, the College reserves the right to remove content which violates the terms of this statement or other relevant policies, but is under no obligation to do so.
